[narrator] Previously on Love Island USA...
There were Raunchy Races...
[laughing]
[narrator]...passionate kisses...
and one boy was feeling the pressure.
-Come here. honey.
-You are really a dangerous creature.
Hey. stop.
[narrator] Tonight...
I got a text.
[all] Oh. shit.
-It's a video.
-[gasps] Stop!
[Kassy] Oh. fuck.
[sobbing] This is so fucked up.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[narrator] Welcome to Love Island USA.
It's full speed ahead.
And while Najah's pursuit of Keenan
is meeting less than stiff resistance.
over in the kitchen.
Allie is trying to get her mum a gig
on the exciting new spinoff show.
Love Island: MILF Edition.
My mom's hot.
so I love going places with her.
Like. she is a dime piece.
[phone chimes]
-I got a text!
-Let's go!
Men tend to gravitate towards people
who remind them of their mothers
or sisters or people that they love.
-[phone chimes]
-Interesting. [gasps]
Ooh! You guys. I got a text!
-[Destiny] She got a text!
-Oh. shit.
[Imani] You got a text?
All right. "Casa Amor and Villa.
as a result of tying in today's
Raunchy Races challenge.
both Hideaways are open."
[all cheering. applauding]
[Kenzo] "Each villa has the option
to choose
one boy and one girl
to share a night alone.
#FinishingFirst. #EveryonesAWinner."
-Bergie!
-[Keenan] Bergie!
Bergie!
How are you feeling. my friend?
You want the Hideaway?
[all cheering]
I'm the first guy this year
to go in the Hideaway twice.
I feel like I'm a completely new person
going back into the Hideaway.
and this time I'm excited.
-[Marco] Back in it.
-[Bergie] Back in it.
Back in it. baby.
[Hannah]
Who are we thinking? Who we thinking?
Zay and Destiny.
[Imani] That sounds good.
[Destiny] The Hideaway!
Oh. my gosh.
We finally get uninterrupted time.
[all cheering. chanting]
-Okay. Hideaway!
-What are we wearing?
[Hannah] Let's go. let's go.
This is definitely a time
to be sexy and fun. and just... You know.
-[Hannah] Yeah!
-You know? I have some options.
We have options. baby girl.
-[Imani] We got options.
-Yay. Destiny! I'm so excited for you.
[all cheering]
[Imani] Okay.
What are you gonna wear. bro?
[Zay]
Maybe I'll just walk out there naked.
Bro. keep the necklace on.
Keep all the jewelry on.
I'm excited
because it'll give Destiny and I
a chance to test out how we are alone.
instead of surrounded by people.
Who the fuck going
to the Hideaway over there?
[Kassy] Bergie. hopefully?
It better be Bergie.
[all laughing]
[all cheering. clapping]
[Jonah] How are you feeling. Bergie?
Nervous? Excited? I don't know.
[all shouting. laughing]
[Keenan] I say you walk out there
in your straight boxers.
-Go buck naked.
-Yeah!
[all cheering]
I'm just looking forward to building
my connection more with Taylor S. tonight.
whether that's physical or just emotional.
I've been waiting for this.
Now I'm going back into the Hideaway.
but this time I feel like
I'm going to get that spark going.
Okay. guys. I actually am excited.
[all cheering. applauding]
What are you feeling. though?
When we were in Soul Ties.
I was like. "I could kiss him."
[Taylor S]
I am feeling butterflies a little bit.
I'm feeling good. feeling sexy.
and I'm ready for the Hideaway.
[all cheering]
[Keenan imitates dog barking]
I will see where just things go
on the romantic level.
But we have good conversation.
He makes me feel comfortable.
[narrator] The Hideaway is the most
erotically-charged room on the planet.
And caught up in the magic.
Destiny and Zay
hug like two distant family members
meeting at Thanksgiving.
-I'm excited!
-Yeah. I like this.
-You like it? We match. We keep matching.
-Mm-hmm.
-We do match.
-Unintentionally.
-Oh. my gosh. This is so pretty.
-Yeah.
[Destiny]
Let's see if this bed comfortable.
That's nice.
-Cheers to the Hideaway.
[Zay] Should we play a game?
No. hell no. we not playing no game.
-Are you tired?
-Yeah. I'm going to sleep.
I'm sorry. I'm so tired.
I'm in the Hideaway with Destiny.
I'm like. "What am I gonna talk about?
What am I gonna say?"
Destiny.
Good night.
[all cheering. applauding]
[Islander] Go. Bergie!
[Marco] Bergie. hold it down. baby!
[all cheering. applauding]
-Holy shit.
-I'm back.
You're back.
What. second time?
-Second time.
Wow. this is crazy.
Oh. we have the champagne.
-No. we don't!
-Strawberries.
-I'll start it. I'll start it. okay?
-Okay.
[clicks tongue] So. cheers to being open.
sexy and single and ready to mingle.
I love that.
Uh. cheers to just
getting to know each other and...
-Just all worked out in the end. Yeah.
-Seeing what happens.
I did not expect this to happen.
So...
are you excited for this?
Oh. 100%.
I'm very open to just
having one-on-one time with you.
-Yeah. It's just. like...
-Yeah. I just want you to. like...
Be just... Feel comfortable. and if...
I don't want you to feel like
you have to put on a front or anything.
And I haven't been with you.
What's your flaw in the whole romantic...
getting romantic with someone?
Honestly. it's just...
I don't know how to cross the barrier.
-What do you mean?
-The physical touch barrier.
Like. I'm not good
at going in for the kiss.
I don't know when to do that.
I don't know if it's 'cause
I'm uncomfortable with it.
But is it because you respect
boundaries too much that...
I think that's it. and I don't know
when I can cross that boundary.
Like.
I'm very physically attracted to you.
I'm physically attracted to you as well.
For sure.
Yeah. and this took me by surprise.
The Hideaway or like...
-Just our conversations.
-Oh.
You're someone
who I do feel comfortable with.
and I wanna get to know more.
Same here.
You've been on my top three.
I'm not gonna lie. since day one.
They got the furry handcuffs.
-Lay down.
-Like...
Put your hands up. Behind your head.
Oh. shit. Oh. no.
[Kay Kay] Would he be wrong
to bring back somebody?
Bro and I is done
if he brings somebody back.
No. no. That's what I mean.
It's done and over with.
But. like. would he do that?
-[Carmen] Probably.
-I don't know.
I honestly don't know.
-I feel like...
-I don't know either.
-And I know everyone...
-I should know.
[Najah laughs]
No. I don't wanna switch sides.
Kassy makes me feel very comfortable.
This bracelet that I have on my wrist
all the time is the one she just gave me.
It's hard
because I miss her so fucking much.
Good night. my squad.
Good night.
[narrator] By the end of it all.
who's sleeping with who?
In Casa Amor.
Imani is with Kyle.
while on their own are Brandon.
Eddie and Rob.
while Carmen. Kay Kay.
and Hannah are sleeping outside.
Destiny and Zay are in the Hideaway.
and Kassy and Matia are getting cozy.
Over in the villa.
Dasja is with Mike.
sleeping alone are Hannah O..
Ashley and Allie.
Marco and Kenzo are outside.
Taylor C.'s sleeping with Jonah.
Najah's with Keenan.
Taylor S. and Bergie are in the Hideaway.
and Johnnie and Leonardo
are in bed together.
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
[Najah] Oh...
Good morning.
Hannah O. Your first night in the villa!
Allie. were you kinda jealous that
Bergie was in the Hideaway without you?
No. I support that.
Taylor's gonna have to take the lead
on this.
Do you think they went all the way?
I don't know. man.
Bergie is just such a gentleman.
-Good morning.
-Here we go. I got some confidence now.
-[laughs] Good.
Tell me about your night. bro.
Yeah.
I feel like you guys stayed up real late.
-Hmm?
-[Hannah O] Hmm?
Okay.
I'm just laying down.
giving her little besitos and then...
went to sleep.
Whoever wins the Rock Paper Scissors
decides who cooks breakfast.
-Mike?
-[Ashley] Okay. ready?
Rock. paper. scissors. shoot.
[Jonah] Mike!
Yeah. Ashley! Yes!
Y'all make breakfast!
[Taylor C] No. for real. You killed that.
-Great job.
-Thank you.
Good morning. boys!
Good morning. guys.
Good morning.
-That was so aggressive.
-It was.
There we go.
No. I'm not knuckling you.
-Wait.
-Stop playing.
I feel. like. good.
[both laughing]
Not much talking going on
over here last night.
-Word?
-No. I'm just kidding.
-It was good. I slept like a baby.
-[groans]
[Leonardo] What type of eggs do you want?
-[Johnnie] Any.
-Any?
[Johnnie] I love all eggs.
All... [chuckles]
-All eggs are rated equal.
-[Johnnie] All eggs...
[both chuckle]
[Jonah] Were you about to bite me?
[Taylor C] No. never.
How do you think. uh.
Bergie feels in that Hideaway?
Oh. man. [chuckles] Sensational.
[Jonah]
I mean. he should feel comfortable.
-He's been in that room before.
-Right?
[Mike] And he grew so much
since that first time.
-Yeah.
-If you say so.
This time around. it's a whole new Bergie.
Iceberg.
[Jonah] Kenzo.
What's your game plan for today?
If any girls come
and pull you for those chats?
Like. when I walked in and I saw Carmen
and. like.
just. like. spoke a few words with her.
like. I instantly knew
there was something there.
My mind's already set.
It's not gonna change.
Carmen. for me. is. like.
the one right now.
And so. obviously.
if she comes back with someone else.
it's gonna fucking suck.
and it might backfire on me.
But I know what we built before she left.
I'm pretty confident about that.
[Jonah] Keenan. you got a game plan today?
Uh. yeah. I mean. obviously.
like I told all you boys.
before this whole experience...
Like. Casa Amor...
I was ready to close things off
with Kay Kay.
I will tell you guys. like.
more and more. I'm starting to miss
Kay Kay a little bit more.
It's because I'm exploring.
because I'm open.
But eventually.
if I don't feel that. like.
"A hundred percent. this is better than
what I have with Kay Kay."
you know. at this point.
what am I doing it for?
You know what I'm saying?
Just for extra cuddles?
If today. at this very second.
I had to make a decision.
I would still go with Kay Kay.
But I am progressing with Najah.
and if I had maybe a day
or two more with Najah.
it might switch in Najah's favor.
It's just... It's tough.
I feel like sooner or later
I'm going to get to that point where
I know exactly what I want.
-Good for you.
-Thank you.
[narrator] Over in Casa.
when they ask Zay what happened
last night in the Hideaway.
he's gonna say absolutely nothing.
Partly because a gentleman never tells.
Mainly because what happened
was absolutely nothing.
Where is Destiny. girl?
Come on out of that Hideaway.
We'll go up to the door. like. "Wake up!"
If you ain't wanking that willy. come out.
[all chuckle]
[Zay] Well. I had fun with you.
[Destiny] Don't say it like that.
-I hated...
-Thank you.
I had fun with you.
[Brandon] It's not every day girls
get to ogle at you like this
while you're working out. It's kinda fun.
-[Kay Kay] Time to show off. huh?
-[Brandon] Yeah. you know it.
-Hey!
-Good morning.
-[Zay] Hello. hello. hello.
-[Destiny squealing]
[Brandon] What's up. brother?
-Hi!
Oh!
Let's go. They can get another chat. come.
[Destiny. Hannah squealing]
[Brandon] We need to hear about this.
-[Hannah] You are glowing.
-Hi. ladies!
You're so rested.
[laughs]
[Hannah] Look at you. You look so pretty.
-Tell us everything.
-Everything.
[chuckles]
I fell asleep on him. y'all.
I ain't gonna lie.
I said. "Look. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. baby.
When I need to sleep. I need to sleep."
Beautiful.
How sweet.
I really am happy that Destiny had
this time in the Hideaway with Zay.
I've never seen her this happy
and smiling.
And I just wanna keep this Destiny.
[Carmen] It's exactly what you wanted.
-That's exactly...
-I love that.
I'm glad it was everything
that you wanted.
[Jonah] Leo. what's your plan for today?
-Wake up.
-I'm sorry.
[laughs]
You have a long night. Leo?
Yeah.
What kept you up? Lotta talking?
Just talking.
[Marco] Jesus.
You look like you're half asleep.
Yeah. bro. I have nothing in the tank.
I don't know. bro. I'm going to have
a conversation with Johnnie.
We're going to keep kicking it.
I'm going to try to. like.
keep things slow and. you know...
[laughs]
...have the conversations I need to have.
So. last night. we were. like.
in bed and he kissed me.
but I think I was just so overexcited.
and it just carried on and on and on.
We were just kissing forever.
And then...
Okay. Was it good?
You know how he has big dick energy?
Like. his personality?
Does it match? The energy matches?
He has big dick energy.
-Like. I was very shocked.
-[laughs]
When we were talking. he said...
[both laugh]
Now he has.
Because I was thinking. like...
People just connect.
It's like. some people connect.
some people don't.
[Johnnie] I like Leo a lot.
I just feel like when you know. you know.
It is terrifying.
But the feelings are feeling.
Yeah.
[sighs]
When there's a vibe. there's a vibe.
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
For Leonardo. discretion is everything.
So. he asked the camera guys
to stand well back
while he tells Marco what happened
last night in graphic detail.
What a gentleman.
[Leonardo] Oh. my God.
[narrator] Destiny. the best-rested person
ever to exit the Hideaway.
wants to know
how the other girls are getting on.
Now. tell me about y'all.
Especially y'all two.
Our connection is so good that even. like.
when we're quiet.
it's. like. comfortable.
and we're just. like. laughing.
Like. man. I like him. girl. I like him.
I love this.
-Ah!
-[Kay Kay] I'm so happy for you.
[Destiny] So. what about you. Kassy?
What happened with y'all?
So. yeah. like.
it feels natural with Matia.
It's not like he's just
somebody I just met.
It's very comforting with him.
And it's nice to have somebody
that's only here for you
and is showing that.
But also. it's nice to reciprocate
and be like. "I actually like you too."
-We'll worry about the villa later.
-Exactly.
[Kassy] Right now. though.
it's all good with Matia.
and I can't. like. deny that. either.
Yeah. I agree.
-So... Yeah.
-[Destiny] I agree.
[Kassy] Matia is potentially
the second guy
I could have a connection with.
But with Leo. it's not just a "like."
It's more than that. It's a stronger bond.
Hopefully I can figure out
soon enough what my feelings mean.
-Can we do a group hug?
-Can we?
Of course.
-[Kay Kay] Love you. girlies.
-[Kassy] Love you all.
[Kay Kay] I wouldn't rather spend
my experience with anyone else.
For real.
We doing this. okay?
[narrator] After Leonardo's confession.
Marco needs to tell Kenzo.
and I need to change Leonardo's bedsheets.
I'll just use the ones
from the Casa Hideaway.
They're as good as new.
[Kenzo] Yeah.
I noticed that this morning. Yeah.
-I trust you. Yeah.
-Yeah. man. Damn.
I don't even know what to tell him.
[Kenzo] That's crazy.
That's insane.
That's got to be his. like...
-Ladies.
-[Islander 1] Hello.
-Hi.
-Hey.
How y'all doing?
-[Islander 2] They're probably listening.
-[Islander 3] They are.
They're eavesdropping over there.
No. they're sharing secrets.
-They're sharing secrets.
-They are.
It's hard to watch.
It's actually hard for me to watch.
Maybe he's lost and trying
to figure something out.
Kassy to Anna. to back to Kassy.
to. "I'm not turning my head.
It's gonna take a lot."
to a day and a half
turning to. you know. Johnnie.
does something with Johnnie...
Oh. my God. Fuck me. Dude. I don't know.
Lost.
[narrator] Hannah and Kay Kay want to know
what their boys have been doing
at Casa Amor.
Hannah. Marco has been
an upright gentleman.
Kay Kay. Keenan's gentleman
has been upright.
Shit has gotten real for me here.
I even miss all the boys.
Is it weird I've been. like. considering
wanting to move and live with Marco?
I don't think it's weird at all.
I think it would be weird if you weren't.
-Okay.
-[laughs]
I don't know how to be apart. [chuckles]
Yeah. because I feel like y'all are there.
You know? Y'all are to the point where
that's a consideration to consider.
you know?
Okay.
Do you think Keenan's
gonna bring someone back?
Since you're asking me.
I don't know.
It's one of those things I...
It could go either way.
I just don't know.
And what he does. Kay Kay.
whatever his decision is.
he's trying to make it
sound good in his head for him.
You get what I mean?
I think that Keenan...
He's definitely an overthinker.
Yeah. for sure.
And I think that he's a little...
What's the word?
He's kind of selfish with his emotions.
Like...
he struggles to see
what other people are feeling
because he's feeling so much.
and that's all he can see.
[narrator]
I'm surprised Keenan is talking to Najah.
I thought him and Kay Kay
were as tight as the crotch
on Keenan's jeans after Najah
flirted with him.
Look at your knees.
See? There you be goin'.
I got fat knees.
I got fat... I got cankles.
-How big is your hands?
-Huh?
How big is your hand?
Over here.
Little. Little. little.
On my hand. this pinky's so crooked.
I don't know what I'm going to do yet.
-About your hands?
-No.
The whole recoupling thing.
I have no idea.
Yeah.
I told you I'm honest and straightforward.
I don't have a clue.
And that's why I... And that's. honestly...
I really do... I like PDA. just like you.
I'm not gonna lie. but until I'm sure.
I don't like doing that to people.
-I don't like...
-You want me to move over?
A little bit.
I don't want you to.
but I need to until I'm sure.
You get what I'm saying?
It's not fair to you. is it?
It's whatever to me.
Be. like...
Stand on it or don't stand on it.
That's not fair.
Like. stand on it and be like.
"I'm going to take it slow."
What's it called? "I'm a slow burner."
Time out. Who be pressing?
You don't be pressing me?
I don't be pressing you?
I say you don't be pressing me.
making it extremely difficult on me?
-I do.
-So. what are you...
That's because I want you.
And that's what I stand on.
I really been a bit struggling.
It's really difficult to navigate.
you know. me getting to know Najah
while being here in the villa.
and not disrespect Kay Kay.
Even though Najah has showed me
verbally and physically her interest.
it is difficult for me
to do a bunch of physical things with her.
You know what I'm saying?
I think. Kay Kay. even if he does
bring someone back.
don't take it personal.
I will. Hannah.
-Yeah... You will?
-I will.
You can't do that.
-Don't do that.
-Okay.
Because she ain't Kay Kay.
She don't got the personality. the beauty.
They don't even...
My dad has a saying.
You'd love my dad. because I feel like.
even though he's not from Texas...
-Yeah.
-...he just reminds me of Texas people.
He's like. "She can't hold your panties."
Every time.
Aw. [giggles]
Every time I'd compete
against a girl in sports.
he's like. "She can't hold your panties."
-[laughs]
-So...
I am not a selfish person.
I cannot just solely act on how I feel.
Of course I feel the vibe.
Of course I feel the chemistry.
Of course I like you.
Of course I'm gonna continue talking.
But I care about that girl's feelings.
I can't just completely disregard
the shit I've been building with her.
Yes. we have our flaws.
Yes. she is not perfect.
But I still have to take
that into consideration.
So if I make this move.
it has to be truly a move
that I feel 100% comfortable with.
-Okay. and I feel that.
-So. it's like. of course...
Because I do have feelings for you.
when you do shit like that.
I can only say no so many fucking times
before I fucking crack.
I'm a fucking man.
Like. I will own it.
I'll be the first to own it.
In here... If we were in the real world.
I could get to know both of you
and figure that out.
But right now it's difficult 'cause
I can't get to know
both of you at the same time.
And I will admit
that I have been extremely happy
these past couple of days.
Everybody's been saying it.
Everybody's all.
"I haven't seen you smile
like that in forever."
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
With the clock ticking down
to decision time.
clothing brand owner Matia's pulled Kassy
to offer her love. support.
and a 15% discount on dresses
if she uses the code "MATIA15"
at checkout.
[Matia] We're gonna have a lot of fun.
-Fun in the sun.
-[Kassy] Yeah. So much fun.
Like. if I was to bring you back
in the villa.
like. would you still be trying to
get to know the rest of the girls?
-No.
-No?
I'm at a point in my life where. like.
if I meet a girl and I like her.
there's a connection there.
like. I don't see a reason
to. like. explore more options.
-Like. what's the point of that?
-Mmm.
Yeah. And I know it's hard for you
to fully be just engaged
'cause you're like... I get it.
-I can't give you 100%.
-That's what I'm saying.
-Yeah.
But you know why.
Oh. of course. I'm completely comfortable
moving at the pace that you wanna move.
Like. I'm not here to rush anything.
And again. I'm not here to play games.
And. like.
if you decide to bring me back.
it's because I wanna continue
to push it forward with you.
And I'm not looking
to get to know other girls.
-Yeah.
-So. yeah.
I don't know how to talk about
my feelings.
-Me neither.
-I'm all awkward and shit 'cause. like.
growing up.
playing sports... My coach. my dad...
we're always taught to just be tough.
"Don't talk about your feelings.
Don't be a wuss."
-So you always held it in?
-Everything. Everything.
I could have the worst day
and people ask me. "How are you?"
I'm like. "Good."
-I struggle with expressing how I feel.
-Yeah?
Yeah. I just. like... I'm saying...
I just mean if I seem a little awkward.
it's 'cause I don't know...
-You're not used to saying how you feel.
-Yeah.
-Yeah. exactly.
[Kassy]
I feel like I'm in love with one guy.
but then I also like another guy.
Like. is that even a thing?
It's just confusing.
But now it's making me feel like.
"Should I explore...
this guy?"
It might be better than what I have
in the villa with Leo.
Yeah. I know your situation's hard.
Yeah.
[narrator] Back at the main villa.
Leonardo's chatting with Taylor C.
about whether he should
go with his head or...
[narrator stammers]
Well. his other head.
It's just hard because. like.
I did not prepare for this shit.
No.
You never can prepare for it.
It just happens.
I could also feel. like. me and Johnnie
are on the same standpoint.
Like. I'm not going to speak for her.
but it's just hard...
because I wish
she never came into this house.
[laughs]
-I wish I never met her.
-It would've been a lot easier.
Life would be so easy if she. you know.
just never came along.
Yeah.
-But she did.
-She did.
Leo. Leo. Leo.
I know. like. as of right now. like.
Kassy still. like.
has that upper hand 'cause she makes me...
She's always made me feel a type of way.
Mm-hmm.
I don't even know what I would do
if she came back in here
and didn't even explore
anything else over there.
'cause I don't know
where her headspace is at.
Mm-hmm.
And then last night. fucking day two...
Yeah. I know.
You got yourself in deep with that shit.
Yeah. really deep. I'm not even gonna lie.
Um...
When she told me this morning.
I was like. "No fucking way."
Yeah. What did she say? [laughs]
All good things.
-She said... She was like. "It happened."
-Girl.
Kind of like what you're saying.
It happened naturally.
-It wasn't a planned thing.
-She wasn't necessarily expecting it.
-Yeah.
-You are in quite a fucking pickle.
-I'm in some heat. Yeah.
-Yet again.
-Yet a-fucking-gain. Like...
Oh. my God.
Kassy's still in the back of my mind
because she's an amazing girl.
so it's just a sucky feeling.
Feeling like you betrayed someone
because. you know.
that's my bed with Kassy.
But at the same time.
this is part of the experience.
to test out where
you really stand with someone.
[Leonardo] At this point. bro.
I may as well just tell you guys
what the fuck happened last night.
Well. let's just say I hit
the home run last night.
[Keenan] No.
-Goddamn. Le.
-I know.
[Keenan] Goddamn. Le.
[Leonardo] But it wasn't my intentions.
[Keenan] Just happened.
[Leonardo] Yeah.
[laughs]
[groans]
[narrator] Rancher Jonah can't wait
to introduce Taylor C.
to Sue. Norma. and Abigail.
That's if his dad hasn't already
taken them to the market.
[Jonah] Are you a morning person?
I actually hate sleeping in
because I feel like I waste half my day.
Yeah.
I don't like sitting around doing nothing.
Do you ever just. like. go for drives?
And just. like...
Dude.
you reading my mind or something?
Can you read my brain?
No.
Really?
I drive all the time.
That's like my therapy.
My dad has a girlfriend.
and she has a five-year-old son.
and they're at the ranch.
Are you close with them?
I feel like he's my son.
Um...
Shit.
He wants to learn all these things.
I love having little kids
that want to look up to you like that.
Well. I put him in a mutton busting.
-Really?
-Yeah.
And he rode a sheep
and they did the whole thing.
Wait. that's so cute.
-And I cowboyed for a couple outfits.
-That's hot.
You seem like one of those guys who can
just be good at anything he does.
I'm really. really enjoying
to get to know Jonah.
I feel like it's still crazy to me
that I've only known him now
for two full days.
He makes me a little nervous sometimes.
Like. in a good way.
He gives me the butterflies.
I literally just forget that
I'm here when I'm talking to him.
Like. it's like I'm transported to
this different world.
You have very pretty eyes.
-You do too.
-Thanks.
-Hmm?
-Mmm.
[narrator] Back at Casa Amor.
Carmen wants to know. in the outside
world. what does Rob go for.
Well. it's mainly boa constrictors.
using a big net and a trash grabber.
You look radiant.
-Do I? Thank you.
-You're welcome.
I haven't even asked you.
Would you say in the outside world.
I would be the kind of girl
that you would go for?
Yeah. but no. at the same time.
-Okay.
-I like that you're...
basically the opposite of me.
You're super type A.
you're super organized.
you want a schedule.
you wanna do all this stuff.
I always say I either want
a girl that's like me
or I want a girl that is
completely opposite of me
because it's like. you could ground me.
and then I could like...
"Get the hell out of your comfort zone."
"Let's go do something you don't wanna do
and let's have fun."
-You know what I mean? I love that.
-It's that good balance.
We have such a good connection.
and we do just bounce back and forth.
and it's so comfy.
-Yeah.
-And we vibe a hundred percent.
But then I think in the outside world.
we don't do any of the same things.
No?
But you look at that as an opportunity to...
-Yeah.
-...get out of your comfort zone.
Yeah. I do.
I wouldn't mind it.
The vibe I get from you is
you're looking for like.
an outdoorsy. like. artsy-fartsy type of
girl. and it's just not me.
Home is a constant comfort for me.
Like. I like to go out for the day
or all of that.
but my biggest relief is coming back
to my space.
Yeah.
I feel bad. I don't want you to feel like
I just think about the bad things.
Like. I fully think we. like...
Our chat is great.
I think we get along so well.
I feel you just think I have a negative...
No. I don't. I see the way you smile at me
and that makes me feel good.
You like me a little bit.
-Yeah.
-I know you do.
I'm definitely very confused
on where I should proceed with Carmen.
She's saying she's still open.
but it doesn't really feel that way.
I very much am just in my head
today about everything.
Okay.
Do you wanna not do that?
No. I just don't want it...
'Cause I am so torn and confused.
Yeah.
-I have so much fun being around you.
-I know.
And you do make me happy
and you make me smile.
-Yes. Yeah.
-It's fun to flirt with you.
And I feel like we have very similar...
flirtation. that it's great.
Mm-hmm.
I can't see her having as much fun
with him as she has with me.
but I just want her to want me. you know?
It doesn't feel like she does.
[smacks lips]
That's sad.
-I just am an overthinker.
-Yes. I know.
-And I need to stop.
-Yeah. you should stop.
No. stop. I'm...
Oh. God.
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
Watching Keenan over the past few days.
we've all been wondering
if he's going to slip up.
And we're about to get our answer.
Hey. fellas. Oh. Cross. cross. Ooh.
Hey.
Played it off.
[Marco] I was thinking.
I wonder if Hannah really meant
to leave me her cross.
It was laid out right in front of it.
the note. I think she meant to.
If it was in front of the note. yeah.
Wasn't like I went in her drawer
and took it.
-Right.
-It was laid out right there.
[Keenan] Does she normally always wear it?
-Yeah.
-Okay. then yeah.
[Keenan]
See. bro. Leo be doing it to himself.
-[Marco] What's he doing?
-He's just doing too... Like. it's day two.
That's too much.
Even though he says. "I'm willing to get
to know other people. have conversations."
it's a contradiction
when you do stuff like that.
It makes it look like he's just hopping
from body to body based upon his lust.
Yeah.
Literally everything happened so fast.
but it didn't feel wrong.
-Yeah.
-And I was questioning. like.
why it didn't feel wrong.
Yeah.
Because seeing how well we just click
and how everything flows naturally...
And you don't seem to be trying.
you're kind of just living and existing.
You know.
you're still being you and doing you.
and I like that a lot.
I warned him way too many times.
Yeah. like. before... Like.
literally two days ago. it was. what?
"It'll take so much
for me to turn my head."
He took her bracelet off.
-He's not wearing it right now?
-[Marco] No.
I could never take this cross off.
-Never.
-[Kenzo] Yeah.
[Keenan] This is just insane. bro.
I thought this experience
was gonna suck like Casa Amor.
because I was going to push everyone away.
And then I gave you the chance of a convo.
That was one of the best conversations
I've had in a long time.
It's funny because I was...
-in here thinking. "I live alone."
-Yeah.
"I am alone all the time
and I like being alone."
Well. I want to be alone.
but. like. where Leo is and be alone.
Like. be alone with Leo.
Yeah. That's such good wording. though.
Like. I want to be alone. but...
-With him right there.
-...be alone with him.
I like the "comfortability."
or the homeness kind of vibe.
Now there's this spark here
that I wasn't prepared for.
but some of the best things in life.
you don't prepare for.
It just kind of happens.
You definitely have my head fucking
scrambled up like some eggs.
-[Kay Kay] I'm climbing on the bumpers.
-[Imani] Des. come here. Hold it.
[Imani] Hold it. There we go.
-I'm on the bumpers.
-She's going.
[Imani] You got it.
[Destiny squeals. laughs]
[Islander] Shit! Oh. fuck!
Yes. she caught me!
-Can I tell you about my convo with Rob?
-Yeah. I saw you guys were talking.
[Carmen] The conversation is great.
If I never met Kenzo and I met Rob.
we could have so much fun in here.
It's just hard to. like.
compare what I have with Kenzo.
-Mm-hmm.
-I want someone that's all for me.
That's always been a big thing for me.
And. like. Rob giving me that energy
does make him more attractive to me.
But I guess we'll all see
how it plays out.
Exactly.
-But I feel like...
-All we have is the what-ifs.
-Yeah.
-Or what can happen.
But how are you feeling?
What are you feeling with Matia?
Like. is it...
It's like the same with you.
I'm not going in a hundred percent
with Matia
only because I know I have
something strong with Leo.
I think if you were in the villa.
you would have told Leo.
"I'm gonna get to know him."
Because you don't have that opportunity.
it's weird.
I feel guilty. It feels like I'm cheating
on him. if I'm being deadass.
Maybe he's cheating on me. I don't know.
But that's what it feels like.
It feels like I'm cheating on him.
And what's so crazy is that. like.
this is the first connection since Leo
where I actually had felt something
when we would talk.
I just want Leo to know
that this isn't easy for me at all.
-Yeah.
-Like. it isn't easy.
I've never had feelings like this before.
It's just... It feels smooth.
It feels comfortable.
What does your gut tell you
Leo's doing back there?
Do you think he's going
to be standing alone?
-No clue? Fifty-fifty?
-Fifty-fifty.
He could be doing
what he did in the beginning.
getting to know girls.
making out with girls.
going in. all in.
Or he could be like. "It's all Kassy."
[narrator] Last night in the Hideaway.
Bergie and Taylor S.
made sweet. sweet music.
Nice move to put a saxophone and a violin
in the cupboard
next to the whip and handcuffs.
We're on the same page
with everything right now. I think.
I just don't wanna keep...
-Yeah. let her go. bro.
-[Bergie] Yeah.
I want to give her some space
and I'll get mine.
Just think about it. you know?
No. no. Yeah. you know what to do.
Yeah. I'm not gonna keep pulling her for...
[Keenan] Fuck. no. That's smothering.
-Yeah. Like... Yeah.
-You know what I'm saying. See? You know.
Bro. she leaves me her cross. bro.
and comes back with another dude.
I might actually cry.
That shit would hurt. I ain't...
That shit would hurt.
But I don't let anybody see me sweat.
But I'd sit there like. "Wow."
I've never felt like this
about a girl in my life.
I'm pretty lost. kind of. I just...
I feel like a part of me left.
And then. you know.
I just haven't been the same since.
like a lost puppy.
[Keenan]
I don't know about Kay Kay. I don't know.
I think she's gonna stay loyal to you.
-[Keenan] You think.
-Like. I'm not...
-[Marco] "Think" is not good.
-[Keenan] You get what I'm saying?
I don't want her to feel like shit
for finding a good connection.
But I'd be pissed. bro. I definitely would
tell her about herself real quick.
but nothing too crazy.
-You'd be done with her though. right?
-[Keenan] Oh. 100%.
-You'd be on the same flight home as me?
-A hundred percent. without hesitation.
-[Marco] 'Cause I was gonna say...
-What's the point...
'Cause I ain't gonna lie. I do
have a good vibe with Najah. I really do.
The physical attraction is there.
Everything is there. bro.
She's pressing me just like how
I would want a girl to.
I'm in a fucking conundrum.
Would you be happy with that?
I'm like. "I don't think you would."
I was like. in the most... not saying...
-[phone chimes]
-[gasps]
Oh. shit.
-[Islander] Oh. shit.
-I got a text!
[all] Oh. shit.
[Kay Kay] What's it say?
It's a video.
[gasps] Stop!
-Oh. no. no. no. no. no.
-[Kassy] Oh. fuck.
"Girls. you have been sent
a story from the villa."
He was sitting there talking.
and I was like.
"You are fucking gorgeous."
He's so hot.
So. I am who you're pursuing?
Yeah. Very apparent.
I just had to hear you say it.
You said it without hesitation.
-You are who I'm pursuing.
-I'm interested.
-Oh. shit. Stop.
-Stop.
-Soul Ties.
-Soul fucking Ties.
-Stop!
-[Keenan] Double that.
-Soul Ties is crazy.
-[shushes]
-[Destiny] Who is that?
-Stop. I can't see.
-Is that Keenan?
-Who is that?
-[Destiny] Who is it?
-[Imani] It is.
-That's Keenan...
-[Islander] My good sir.
how did you sleep?
-I slept good. The bed hella comfortable.
-Stop. Stop.
-I Had a nice little cuddle.
-Oh. shit.
-And yeah. Yeah.
-Stop. Kay Kay...
Oh. my. That's...
That's... Bro. that's my ex. That's my ex.
-Stop! Stop!
-Where's Hannah?
-That's my ex-girl. bro.
-Stop. Stop. Stop.
Oh. shit.
-What's up?
-Where's Hannah?
I feel as if we didn't give ourselves
a fair chance.
Oh. fuck. Stop. stop. stop.
We fucked.
-"We fucked"?
-[Destiny] Who is that?
-What?
-Who said that?
-She said. "We fucked." She said...
-[shushes]
Okay.
Was it good?
He has big dick energy.
Who did she fuck?
Soul Ties is crazy.
[all] Soul Ties is crazy.
[Islander 1] That shit's crazy.
-[Islander 2] Soul Ties is crazy.
-Wait. did y'all get the text. too?
[Brandon] No. Can we come over?
-[Kassy] Yes. yes. Come. come.
-[Islander 3] No.
[Kassy] Oh. shit.
-The Avengers.
-Avengers level.
Stop. stop. Okay. y'all want to see?
Y'all want to see?
-[Brandon] Come behind you.
-Where's Hannah?
-[Kay Kay] Where's Hannah?
-[Kassy] We need Hannah.
-I can't watch it again.
This is so fucked.
I need a fucking minute.
[Kassy] Hannah. you need to see something.
-Sorry. guys. I'm so sorry.
-[Carmen] Stop. Stop. Stop.
-You're scaring me. You're scaring me.
-[Kay Kay crying]
We got a video from the villa.
-You just have to see it.
-Can I see it?
-Yeah. so. do you want me to tell you...
-No.
-Just let me see it.
-Just let her see it. Just let her see it.
-[Carmen] Can you come here? Kay Kay.
-[Kassy] I'm so sorry. Kay Kay.
-[Kassy] I'm so sorry.
-[Kay Kay sobbing]
[Kassy] I'm so sorry.
-[Carmen] Let me see.
-[Kassy] I'm so sorry...
[Kassy] Let me see.
-I'm so sorry.
-Come on. Let's go sit on the couch.
I'm so sorry. It's okay.
[sobbing continues]
[sobbing]
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
At Casa Amor.
the girls are still coming to terms
with the video message they've received.
Let me see.
-Let me see. please.
-[Brandon] Start it again. Start it again.
Wait. just start the whole video again.
He was sitting there talking.
and I was like.
"You are fucking gorgeous."
Like. he's so hot.
So. I am who you're pursuing?
Yeah. It's very apparent.
I just had to hear you say it.
You said it without hesitation.
You are who I'm pursuing.
I'm interested.
-[Imani] It's okay.
-Stop.
Don't make me blush.
You know. I'm finna turn purple.
-I'm good with that.
-Clink.
Okay. this is what they want to do.
This is what... Yeah. Okay.
Oh. my... That's... Bro. that's my ex.
-That's my ex.
-What?
-That's my ex-girl. bro.
-[Keenan] What did I fucking say?
-Oh. shit.
-What's up?
I feel as if we didn't give ourselves
a fair chance.
[Kay Kay cries]
Fuck him. dude. Fuck him.
-Literally fuck him.
-[Imani] Let's have a seat. okay?
Let's just... Let's...
It's not you. It's okay.
[Kay Kay breathes shakily]
You saw what you needed to see.
Move on. Close that door. Please. Kay Kay.
For you. close that door.
There's your answer. Kay Kay.
There's your answer. Fuck him.
-Fuck that.
-[Imani] Yeah.
[Hannah] I'm not worried about her.
Where's Kay Kay?
I'm worried about this shit.
That girl doesn't...
That doesn't even compare to who I am.
[Brandon] So fucked.
Fuck him. Kay Kay.
At the end of the day.
what did we need to know?
And now you know.
That's... He's fucked up.
You see her. and you see you?
There's nothing.
Nothing.
-Okay?
-[sobs]
There's nothing.
So. that just shows
that has nothing to do with you.
[sobbing] This is so fucked up.
It's fucked up as fuck.
-I was nothing but loyal to him...
-You've been nothing but loyal.
But that just shows it's not you.
It's him.
And the first chance he gets.
you're right. he showed his ass.
So. now we know.
[Kay Kay sniffles]
And he's stupid. He's stupid.
He's the biggest dumbass.
He showed us this. this. this and that
while you're sleeping outside?
Well. he can't have you.
He can't have you.
-No. because you're too good for that.
-It's done.
-It's fucking done.
You're too good for this.
Keenan's fucking canceled.
I'm gonna fucking kill him.
Is that too much? Like...
[Kassy] Dude. who fucked the brunette?
Who the fuck fucked the brunette?
Because that's definitely Leo's type.
-The brunette.
-The brunette? Yeah.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
I'm not tripping because this man told me
he's falling for me. he's closed off.
And if he wants to go back to the ex.
go back to the ex.
I'm still going to stand by what I said.
I still said I'm falling for him
and I'm closed off to him.
I'm standing by what I said.
So. if he wants to show his ass.
that's on him.
No. no. no. That was another girl.
Because I was looking at the hair.
His ex had light brown hair.
-That girl had dark black hair.
-Okay.
So who... She probably fucked
one of the guys. Fucking Jonah.
Fucking...
[Kassy] No. that one...
Yes. that's definitely Leo's type.
-She fucked...
-'Cause she said. "We fucked."
[Imani]
Then the other girl high-fived her.
-Why are you fucking high-fiving?
-[Imani] Yeah.
[Imani] Okay. This is crazy.
[Kassy]
That's... That has to be Leo's type.
So. if she fucked Leo. I'm done.
No. he likes blondes too.
There's three blondes. Kassy.
[Carmen] No. that's not Leo's type.
-No.
-Okay.
But who do you all think she fucked?
Yeah. it hurts and we get hurt.
but then what do we do?
We come back. because you know
who the fuck you are.
Fuck that.
You're Kay Kay.
You're good.
because you're going to move accordingly.
Yeah.
Keenan in bed with someone.
so take your pick.
Okay.
-Noted.
-Fuck this.
[sniffles]
I feel dumb as fuck. That's how I feel.
I feel like the stupid loyal girl
who has fallen for a guy who...
falls for every goddamn girl
who looks his way.
I just don't get it.
Like. why does it happen to me?
I don't get it. It just feels like no
matter what I do. it's not good enough.
I have literally made so many compromises.
I've been patient with him.
I freaking had sex with him
in the Hideaway.
I've given this man
every single part of me.
and it still has not been enough for him.
Every time I follow my heart.
it gets broken.
Every time.
It's done.
[narrator] Next time...
The Casa Amor recoupling
means a whole new villa.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-